odgirl.com 2015-10-13

# Privacy Statement - Sexy Costumes, Sexy Halloween Costumes, Party Costumes, Adult Customes, Fantasy Costumes, Lingerie

This privacy policy is effective as of January 1st, 2004.

## Information Collection and Use

ODgirl.com is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy. We collect information from our customers to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information, such as order confirmations and order status updates. Information collected includes your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, e-mail address, and payment information such as your credit card number. We also require you to submit a username and password of your choice for your future access to your account information. To safeguard that your user name and password remain confidential, DO NOT share this information with anyone. If you elect to receive our newsletter or special promotions, your contact information will be used for the delivery of these items.

## Registration

In order to process your orders placed on this website, you must first complete the registration form. During registration, you will be required to provide your contact information, which includes your name, e-mail address, telephone number and street address. This information is used to provide you with important ODgirl.com services such as automated order status updates via e-mail.

## Order

Most of the information collected in the registration process will be used to process orders. During the order process, you will have to provide financial information such as your credit card number, expiration date, money order, wire transfer or check information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this contact information to get in touch with you. To properly process your credit card information, we must share your personal and financial information with the merchant bank for authorization and approval. This process is protected by an enhanced security system. See the Security section below for more details on security measures and procedures. We do not share your personal and financial information with any third parties, except those specified in the Sharing section of this policy.

## Cookies

We customize certain Web page content based on your browser-type or other information provided by our cookie. If you reject the cookie, you will still be able to browse our site; however, you will be unable to use our shopping cart and purchase items. This is because cookies are required by the shopping cart to retain the necessary information to process your order. If you disable cookies, ODgirl.com will be unable to accept your order online. We do not share any personally identifiable information provided by this cookie with any third party. Cookies are used only for the purpose of providing you with a personal experience at ODgirl.com.

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information, and we do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties.

## Sharing

We may employ third party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include order fulfillment, package delivery, marketing assistance, postal and e-mail delivery, customer service, data analysis, and credit processing. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for other purposes.

As our business continues to evolve, we may acquire or sell business units or subsidiaries. Customer information is one of the business assets that would be transferred in these types of transactions. In such a situation, your personally identifiable information would only be used in a manner consistent with our pre-existing Privacy Notice.

In the interests of creating a safer marketplace, ODgirl.com will disclose its customers' personally identifiable information to law enforcement or third party fraud protection companies whenever such disclosure is required by state or federal law.

## Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that ODgirl.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website.

## Security

ODgirl.com takes precautions to protect its customers' information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

When our registration/order form asks you to enter sensitive information (such as your credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software currently available in the industry - SSL. ODgirl.com uses the most advanced form of SSL software available: 128-bit encryption by Verisign. To learn more about SSL, follow this link www.verisign.com.

Access to all of our users' information is restricted. ODgirl.com operates in a secured and locked facility that requires all employees to check in and wear valid ID badges. Security cameras are positioned throughout the building in conjunction with multiple alarm systems. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. If you wish to have your financial information removed at the time of your order, you may opt to have your financial information deleted from our records upon completion of your order. Otherwise, you may contact us at service@odgirl.com to request that your information be deleted from our database. For future transactions, you will be required to re-enter your information.

All ODgirl.com servers, including web servers and database servers, are housed and maintained in secure locations. Access to the database is strictly monitored and protected from outside access. Internet access is restricted and protected by multiple Checkpoint and firewalls and password protection. The servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secured environment, inside a secured and locked room. All backups are stored and locked in a high-level security room. Only personnel with proper security clearance have access to these restricted areas. Tape backups are not permitted to leave the premises without prior authorization.

All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy and of what they can do to ensure that our customers' information remains protected.

If you have any questions about ODgirl.com's security practices, you can send us an email at [customerservice@odgirl.com](mailto:customerservice@odgirl.com).

## Special Offers

Our special offers are sent only to customers who grant ODgirl.com permission to send them such information.

To honor the privacy of our users, we offer the option to not receive these types of communications. At the time of your order, you may opt to not receive special offers and news by clicking the appropriate field. Furthermore, all special offers are sent via e-mail and have a "remove link" if you wish to no longer receive special offers and news. Otherwise, customers may occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals or news. Please see the Choice/Opt-out section below for further details on how to be removed from our mailing list should you choose to be removed.

## Correction/Updating/Reviewing Personal Information

Customers may change or review their stored account information such as street address or e-mail address through our website by visiting our Help section. You must have your username and password in order to access your account. In the event you forget both your username and password, please contact our customer service department for assistance.

## Choice/Opt-out

For customers who wish to optout and stop receiving ODgirl.com special offers and related news, ODgirl.com provides several ways to do so. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may optout of receiving these communications by un-checking the "permission to send" field when processing their orders. They may also send e-mails to service@odgirl.com with a request to be removed. Finally, they may use the link provided in all ODgirl.com communications to automatically unsubscribe.

## Notification of Changes

If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users can then choose to allow or to not allow ODgirl.com to use their information in this different manner. Unless Odgirl.com provides a notification of this kind and receives your permission, ODgirl.com will only use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

## Un-Subscribe

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive mail list messages.

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.
